americangeneral.com 2015-06-22

# Privacy - American General Life Insurance Company

American General Life Insurance Company Privacy Notices 

This notice has been sent to certain customers under the Financial Services Act, commonly known as the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act. It explains how nonpublic personal information about you is handled by the insurance company and other affiliates of American General Life Insurance Company.

  * Privacy Notice  

**  
Website Privacy Policy**

This policy explains what information we may gather through this Internet site and how that information is handled and used. 

  * Internet Website Privacy Policy

 **Privacy and Protection of Social Security Numbers**

It is the policy of American General Life Insurance Company to protect customer and employee Social Security numbers that we collect in the course of our business as confidential. This includes maintaining physical and electronic security procedures to guard against unauthorized access to Social Security numbers. We also limit access to Social Security numbers, by among other means, only granting access to Social Security numbers to our employees who use that information to perform their job-related duties. In addition, we do not disclose Social Security numbers to third parties, except where required or permitted by law.

This Notice is provided to you for informational purposes only. You are not required to take any action in response to this Notice, but please review it carefully. This Notice tells you about the ways in which American General Life Insurance Company may use and disclose your protected health information (PHI) and your rights concerning your PHI. PHI is information about you, including demographic information (like your name, address, or gender), whether oral or recorded in any form or medium, that can reasonably be used to identify you. This information may be collected from you or from members of the health care industry (like doctors or employee benefit plans) and relates to your past, present or future physical or mental health or condition, the provision of health care to you or the payment for that care.
